Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
Hurry!
Open the door!
You're Gao Zhiyao, right?
Rookie.
Why do you always
lose your ID badge?
-Ow!
-Be quiet.
Why are you lying here?
Why are you yelling?
Someone tried to grab my hand just now.
I tried pepper spraying him
and sprayed it on myself.
Are you dumb?
Trying to spray someone else
and spraying yourself instead.
Why are you even here?
I'm on duty, aren't I?
Keep it down!
Did you pull the alarm?
Was it you?
I... I pulled the alarm?
I don't know!
All I know is my eyes really hurt now.
-Okay, stop talking.
-What’s wrong?
Can you please take me to rinse my eyes?
Fine, get up.
Keep it down.
Lower your voice!
Counselor, it's nothing.
He sprayed himself
with pepper spray
and accidentally hit the alarm.
I'll take him to rinse it off.
Okay, go ahead.
Hurry, take me to rinse my eyes.
Am I going to go blind from this?
Come on, people are trying to sleep!
So dumb.
[Chihuahua Zhang Longji,
Cell Block 2, Cell 25 A]
[OOPS! I'M IN JAIL]
[Episode 2]
I need a small favor from you.
Get me a deck of
playing cards with nude girls printed.
This won't do.
It's too obvious.
Caught you!
Little girl.
Don't eat your boogers.
That's gross.
I can only give you one card per day.
An ace and a seven for you.
What are you doing?
Morning exercises.
[Bible]
Thank you, Lord, for giving me strength
and blessing me with a beautiful day.
Hallelujah!
Time for work.
Morning.
Zhiyao.
Are you religious?
Yes.
Yes, the inmates take
education classes,
so I thought I could
learn more to help everyone.
So studious.
Can I take a look?
No.
I usually write
personal notes in my Bible.
-Good morning, Counselor!
It's not very convenient.
Okay.
That's not right.
Shui, your inspections are too lax.
You need to be more thorough.
This creates security risks.
Fine, I went easy on you
because you're one of us.
Alright.
Check the back too.
Hey.
Isn't that the guy
who kicked you in the balls yesterday?
Thank you, Shui.
Excuse me, Counselor,
sorry to bother you,
but could you help me?
Could you cover for me?
I can't. I'm from
the Education Division.
But you can do it. Please.
I need to use the bathroom.
Everything's about to come out, you know?
-Shui, I’ll call someone for you.
-Just for a moment!
-Shui!
-I’ll be right back!
Next.
Next one.
Can't believe it.
I'm suddenly being searched by you.
I didn't even put makeup on today.
Do you know who he is?
-Who?
Jiang Yijie.
Top of the police academy.
and promoted to counselor
in just two years.
Plus, his dad the Warden
of Central Prison.
The Warden?
So he's a nepo baby.
Damn.
This is prohibited. You can't bring it.
This is my eyebrow razor.
For grooming this.
I understand, but it's still contraband.
But I've always been allowed before.
The standard rule
is that it's not allowed.
Come back after work to get it.
Next.
Can you go first?
Hurry up.
Come on, next.
Your turn.
Are your eyes okay?
My eyes are fine now. Thanks...
Thanks, Senior.
You need to be proficient
with pepper spray and stun guns.
Otherwise, it could be dangerous
in emergency situations.
Yes. Thank you for the reminder, Senior.
Alright.
By the way, I noticed...
You weren't actually scheduled last night.
I also found
that I misread
the shift schedule yesterday.
I misunderstood Director Xiao.
Misread the schedule?
Senior, if there's nothing else,
I'll be going now.
-Bye-bye.
-Wait.
Are those two dating?
Senior, this is a Bible.
Should be no problem, right?
No problem at all.
Just taking a quick look.
No, it's not that.
I've written some personal notes inside.
It's rather private.
I don't want to read your journal.
It's private!
-What's going on?
-Good day, Warden.
The Warden.
-It's private.
Good day, Warden.
Strange.
Why are you doing the body searches?
Warden.
I'm sorry.
I just went to the toilet,
so I asked Counselor to help.
Come here.
Body searches
are done by the Custody Division.
-Why is the Education Division doing it?
-Tibao,
you run fast.
This morning, the central station's phone
wasn't hung up properly.
Go notify everyone the boss is here.
Tell them the Warden is here. Hurry.
Okay.
Even if he asked you,
you shouldn't do it.
Just focus on your own responsibilities.
Senior, the boss is here for inspections!
Hurry.
My grandfather got married that day
and
he married someone
who was only 20 years old.
Senior, nurse,
the boss is inspecting.
Report!
Why are you running?
Boss is here for inspections!
Was the phone not hung up properly?
Why wasn't the phone hung up?
Quickly report
that the boss is inspecting.
What the hell are you doing?
Teacher.
The boss is inspecting!
Why isn't the social worker
with the chaplain?
Hello, Warden.
Today's rehabilitation activities
require security personnel,
so I came to discuss it with the director.
We'll review the staffing arrangements
at the next meeting.
-Alright?
-Thank you, Warden.
What the hell is wrong with you?
You can't even hang up
the central station's phone?
Are you an idiot?
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
Why did you come here yesterday
for no reason?
Was it even your shift yesterday?
I... misread the schedule.
Misread the schedule?
He misread the schedule.
What's wrong with you?
Why are you letting
any random person in here?
He's a rookie.
What are you? Senior rookie?
Jesus said, “Do not forbid him,
for no one
who works a miracle in my name
will soon afterward
be able to speak evil of me.
For whoever is not against us
is for us."
[Event of Spreading Love and Care]
Amen.
-Amen.
Brothers,
you all sound so lifeless,
like you're falling asleep.
Please play the music.
He's sitting so close to the front.
Come on, everyone. Please stand up.
Let's move around a bit.
Sing along together.
Feel the joy that God gives us.
Get up.
Senior.
Come on, let's cheer together!
Very good!
Hello, Warden.
H-Hello, Warden!
You all look energetic. Great!
This class is going very well.
What are you doing here?
I wanted to come learn
before my shift.
Stop the music for a moment.
Actually, I've been baptized for 30 years.
Come.
Warden, this is my personal Bible.
I didn't expect you to be so devout.
Let me see it.
May I?
Everyone,
You should all
be like this student here.
Read and study God's words every day.
Let God move from the page
into your hearts.
-Yes.
-Amen!
Amen.
How about this? Test me.
Read any passage.
Senior, do you go to church?
Do you have to be so close?
My eyesight is poor.
Alright.
Please read.
God’s will is that we should be holy,
avoiding sexual immorality.
That each of you should know
how to control your own body
in holiness and honor,
not in the passion of lust
like the Gentiles who do not know God.
How was that? Did I recite it correctly?
-Yes.
The Warden recited it correctly.
The Warden spoke wonderfully.
Right.
Everyone,
the Bible is the best gift
from heaven.
I sincerely hope you will take time
to appreciate it
and discover the wisdom of life
and the source of existence within.
Okay?
Okay!
Well said, Warden!
Great!
Oh, right.
Also...
Warden!
This is really quite personal.
There are many
of my personal reflections in there.
That's true.
Our prison
deeply respects
the rights of the inmates.
Personal privacy is very important too.
That's right.
Students,
you should learn from this student here.
Believe that God is always by our side.
-Yes!
The Warden spoke wonderfully.
Excellent.
Counselor, what are you doing?
Reporting, Warden. I...
I suspect some students
are hiding contraband in their Bibles.
Are you all?
No.
No, we're not.
Did you find anything?
No.
Then I would ask our Counselor
not to casually suspect
our inmates, alright?
Come on, continue with the music!
Continue with the music.
Come on, start singing.
Let's end by giving thanks together.
Thank the Lord, thank God.
Reporting, Warden.
My stomach is not feeling well.
It's been days.
I'd like to go to the Health Division
for a check-up.
Alright, administrator,
take this student to the Health Division.
Take him to the Health Division, hurry up.
Quickly, take him.
To the Health Division, quick.
Hurry.
What did you eat?
[Medical Center]
What did you just eat?
High blood pressure medication.
You have high blood pressure?
I will soon.
Okay, take some digestive medicine first.
Here, water.
Let me measure your blood pressure.
Do you have any other discomfort?
I'm feeling great now.
Or would you like to go back
to your cell to rest?
I'm feeling unwell again.
Okay.
Hey, bro.
I don't care what you're planning,
but you can tell your sister
I want 100,000 for those playing cards.
I didn't get a single card.
What are you talking about?
Here, here's one.
How is it?
Okay, let me take your temperature.
37.3.
There's a crease on the nipple.
What did you just say?
I said, you little girl
have very good service.
Thank you.
Does it matter?
Why is your blood pressure so high?
Is it high?
Maybe it's because I saw you.
Sir, stop joking around.
Do you know this could very likely
lead to complications?
What complications?
It could cause a stroke.
I'll report to the supervisor
about escorting you to the hospital.
Here you go.
100,000.
Look at this.
Talking to Chihuahua,
gotta be a gentleman.
Here comes the troublemaker.
Dare me to report you.
If you swallow this card now,
I'll pretend this never happened.
Hurry up, give it to me.
Counselor.
Fine.
-Counselor.
-Hurry up.
He seems to have something in his mouth.
What are you eating?
Are you hiding something? Let me see.
What's going on?
Zhang Longji.
What are you playing with over there?
-You’re disgusting.
-Yijie.
Xiao.
Director.
Are you okay?
Everything's okay.
Help him up slowly.
Watch his head.
Director Xiao,
his blood pressure is already at 200.
He must be taken to the hospital
or else...
I'm really worried.
Okay, but I don't have anyone available
for escort duty.
I can go by myself.
I'll come back.
I know you're just saying crap.
Need an escort to the hospital?
I'll go.
Director, don't want him.
Let this rookie take me instead.
It's a special situation.
Director, he scares me.
Can it not be him?
You're being picky now?
Gao Zhiyao.
You go with him.
Gao Zhiyao, may I ask
why No. 9568 is eating cookies?
Doesn't he have high blood pressure?
And, excuse me, where did he
get the cookies?
I have high blood pressure,
but I also have low blood sugar.
Senior, our gear looks so cool.
And we even have tasers.
It looks like we're shooting a movie.
like John Wick.
You're dead.
I wasn't ready. One more time.
Dead again.
One more time.
And you're dead again.
Dead yet again.
Move again and I'll tase you, I swear.
Be careful at the hospital.
If something goes wrong,
we'll be in big trouble.
[Emergency]
Okay, thanks.
Want to add me on LINE?
How inappropriate.
I'm sorry.
Your hands are cuffed
and you're still horny.
I'll come find you tonight.
Bro, seriously.
How many eye-pleasing pictures
do you want?
I'll find a way to get them for you.
You're outside now.
Don't cause any trouble.
How about this?
Get me some
nude photos of elderly people.
That's terrible. So inappropriate.
You already have high blood pressure.
And what's that blood pressure medicine
you took?
You still get horny after taking it.
That's a happy pill.
Take it and you can come get happy.
My stomach hurts.
I need to take a dump.
For real?
Does it look like I'm faking it?
Senior.
He needs to take a dump.
You take me there.
You take me.
-Don't want him.
-Why?
I don't want him.
He needs to take a dump.
You're really troublesome.
How many times do you need to go?
I have a good digestive system.
I can't control it.
Hurry up!
Here, fill out the rest.
At the bottom, and then this one below.
I'll take him.
What? You need to fill out forms
just to take a dump?
Senior, how do I fill this out?
I just got here. I don't know how.
He needs to learn too?
I'm seriously about to soil my pants.
By the time you finish learning,
I'll be done pooping.
Sit down!
-I'm gonna explode.
-Sit down!
I'm sorry.
No noise in the hospital.
Lower your voice.
-Lower your voice.
-Sit down.
I'm sorry.
-Then hurry up.
-Sit down first.
You're still filling out the forms.
You take him.
I'll fill this out.
Okay.
Be careful.
No. 9568, the toilet is over there.
Thanks.
Are you going to do it or not?
Are you leaving or not?
Can I have some privacy
for using the bathroom?
Didn't you say you were about to explode?
How can I go with you standing here?
Are you two...
Ma'am, you've misunderstood.
How is it? Do you like it?
Fine, I'll wait for you outside.
Hurry up.
Ma'am, you've got it wrong.
I'm just supervising him.
Ma'am, are you feeling unwell?
Ma'am, please rest over there.
Let me help you.
Okay.
I'll get some water first.
Wait for me.
Why is your little buddy hanging out?
I was about to use the bathroom.
Ma'am, were you eating porridge?
Would you like to rest over there?
Thank you.
Good, that's fine now. Thank you.
Here, drink some warm water first.
Are you feeling better?
If you still feel unwell,
remember to make an appointment.
Okay, thanks.
Thank you.
Gao Zhiyao, what are you doing?
She just vomited all over the floor.
I'm helping her clean up.
Where's No. 9568?
He's in the bathroom.
Are you okay now? Take care of yourself.
Gao Zhiyao.
Where's No. 9568?
How long has he been out of sight?
-Well...
-How long? Hurry up.
Just now, not long ago.
Let's split up and search.
I'm screwed.
He probably hasn't gone far.
I'm done for, Senior.
Will I go to jail if we can't find him?
Let's check the security cameras first.
-Okay.
-Let’s go.
Senior, what are you going to do?
Ask them for the security footage.
No, don't.
If you ask them for help,
won't that make this a bigger issue?
I'll get punished.
I'll be the one punished.
You'll be expelled.
Do you have a better idea?
I have an idea.
-Wait for me.
-What?
Don't be rash. I have a solution.
Where are you going?
Let's go check it out.
Everything seems normal.
There is a fire emergency.
Please evacuate immediately
toward the emergency exits.
Attention, everyone!
There is a fire emergency.
Please evacuate immediately
toward the emergency exits.
Senior!
They all came out.
They're all out. What's wrong?
Did you pull the alarm?
Are you crazy?
Why are you making things worse?
Hurry! They'll be back soon.
Such good habits.
Hey! What are you doing?
Great!
Now we can add vandalism to the charges.
Hurry!
Isn't that the volunteer from earlier?
What's their relationship?
Yeah, right.
Is that lady drinking porridge?
So that lady was part of their plan?
That's too much!
They took advantage of my sympathy.
He escaped during this time.
Where are they going?
-The ninth floor.
No. 9568 must have been
holding it in for too long.
So wild.
He's turned himself into a wild beast.
She's not going to jump up there, is she?
She actually jumped up.
Having fun?
Enjoying the show?
He's missing
and you're still laughing?
I'm looking at...
the room number. It's 9...
Wait, zoom in.
-9A12.
Senior, you...
It's the ninth floor.
Why didn't you take the elevator?
I didn't see it earlier.
You could've seen it
by rounding the corner.
Where are we going now?
Want more?
Yes.
You pervert!
You big lecher!
You're messing with me again.
Come on, let me introduce you all.
My wife.
Unlucky guy, annoying guy.
He's hot.
Really?
Hello, I'm Elsa.
I just wanted to
give him a health check-up.
Everything is healthy.
Just some areas
that are blocked, you know.
So I helped clear them out.
Prostate care.
Handcuff him.
Give me your hands.
Is this how you want to play?
You little tease.
Isn't this exactly what you like?
-I like it.
-I’m glad you do.
Can we stop playing now?
Or would you both like to go to prison?
Can we?
-Zhiyao.
-You can sleep with me.
But is your room big enough?
Or should we request a double suite?
Great!
What about using the bathroom?
Get down now.
So fierce, yet so cute.
As cute as me?
He's the ugliest one in there.
Where did you find this hot guy?
Thank you, hottie.
I'm still here.
I've already gone through
two rounds with you.
Turn around.
Put your hands behind your back.
About what happened at the hospital today,
I'll request
disciplinary action for myself.
There you go again.
No.
Can you stop being so stubborn every time?
This isn't a small matter.
No, he's just a rookie,
so the responsibility is on me.
He's a rookie,
so the responsibility should be on me.
Right? I was the one who sent you there.
No, according to protocol,
I should request disciplinary action.
And I will do it.
According to protocol,
it's the Custody Department's problem.
The Custody Division's problems
are my responsibility.
I'll take the blame.
I should take responsibility, that's it.
Fine.
Zhiyao caused some damage
at the hospital today.
The hospital said they'll send us a bill.
What kind of damage?
Anyway, when you get the bill,
give it to the director.
You'll have to handle the director.
You handle everything.
Thank you.
I'll go write my report first.
Sorry for the trouble. Thanks.
-Wait.
-I’ll write the report.
Yijie, wait.
Hey, talking about money hurts feelings.
What's this about?
What damage? Tens of thousand of dollars?
What is he,
the Terminator?
I'm back.
So energetic.
Zhongwen.
Is this yours? Can I have a bite?
Did your hospital escort duty
go smoothly today?
No. 9568 played me.
I almost lost him.
Lost?
I'm glad you didn't lose him.
Otherwise, you'd lose your job
and have criminal liability.
Are you serious?
No.
You can try it.
But with your IQ,
just try not to lose yourself.
But you just got here and already
assigned to external medical escort duty.
I think that's pretty good.
It should help with
getting a permanent position later.
Zhongwen, is there more?
I bought extra.
Do you want me to microwave it for you?
-Wait for me.
-Thank you.
Do you want some soup?
It's too salty. I might need a dialysis.
Hey, the washing machine is still running.
Don't use the microwave yet,
or the power will...
Go out.
Sorry.
Is everything okay?
No.
Next room then.
Thank you, Officer.
Thank you for your hard work, Officer.
Excuse me.
Please squat down again.
Counselor, is something wrong?
Well, I received information that
there are prohibited items in this cell.
Who said that?
There's no problem.
We just finished checking.
Everything is in compliance.
That's right.
Officer, we've been good.
Sorry,
but please squat down.
Squat down.
How did you conduct your inspection?
Everything is neatly arranged.
Did you really inspect this?
Is being neat a problem?
What's wrong with being clean and proper?
We're neat.
That's right.
My inspection methods
are more... effective.
What methods?
The method of turning a blind eye?
We'll inspect again.
Officer,
you've been very concerned
about me lately.
I'm a counselor.
I care about everyone here.
You just gave me demerits
for violations earlier,
and now you're personally
conducting routine inspections?
Your status is different from others here.
Officer,
I have a question I'd like to ask.
If I went out
and left the guard's sight
without permission,
and got demerits for that violation,
then what about the guard in charge?
Thank you for your concern.
I've already requested
disciplinary action for myself.
Requested for yourself?
Did you get any demerits?
Will you get transferred?
Watch your attitude.
Sorry, Officer.
Or did Daddy just give you
a little spank on the butt?
Ouchie!
How's it going? Did you find anything?
Found some things.
Wow, No. 9568.
So many cigarettes.
No, those are within the allowed limit,
right, Shun?
No, they're way over the limit.
Really?
What are you doing? You want to sell them?
And what's this? Sorghum liquor?
This is really unfair.
I've never even seen that thing.
What's that?
Whose is it?
Officer, reporting!
They're all mine.
I accept my punishment.
Bad apple!
What's going on with this cell block?
Don't you care about losing points?
Don't want family visits anymore?
No, we're afraid.
Officer, please have mercy.
It won't happen again.
This also...
This was also just found now?
It was well hidden.
Wow, No. 9568.
Excuse me,
whose raunchy cards
are these?
If I were you,
I wouldn't hold those cards so close.
So dirty.
Shun.
Confiscate everything.
Give demerits as required.
Time's up.
My head hurts so much.
Can you massage it more?
You need to pay more.
So materialistic.
I'm the boss
and I'm serving you personally.
You should be grateful
I'm not charging double.
Fine.
Come on.
What's giving you this headache?
My son, of course,
and the prison.
It's frustrating. There's no solution.
Sometimes, just thinking about it
makes my blood pressure spike.
Speaking of blood pressure...
Here, for your blood pressure.
Remember to take it.
More health supplements?
Thanks.
You got to take care of yourself
at your age.
How does it feel?
Dad, is your health okay?
Why are you buying so many supplements?
Come on, don't worry about
the supplements.
Let's eat.
Dad.
Did you remove my disciplinary report?
You think I'm protecting you?
I never thought about
if you're protecting me or not,
but I've said before that
I don't want special treatment.
If I make mistakes,
I should face the consequences.
Fine.
If I let this issue become public,
and everyone gets inspected daily,
would that be better?
Do what should be done.
Yijie.
I really don't know
if your goal is to climb the ladder
or to study why people commit crimes.
Anyway, if you want to stay here,
there are certain rules
you must understand.
The cell block expansion needs funding.
This year, the Central Prison
Must. Not. Have. Problems.
Understand?
So for the sake of expansion,
rights and wrongs don't matter anymore?
Things have different priorities.
Let me emphasize again.
This year, the Central Prison
Must. Not. Have. Problems.
Let's eat.
[Parole Review
and Assessment Scale for Inmates]
No results.
Custody Division, document delivery.
Seniors.
Is Miss Fang not here?
Where is her desk?
Over there.
Thank you.
Gao Zhiyao,
why does Jieyu get a drink?
I accidentally kicked her prisoner
last time.
It's an apology.
Senior, here are the documents.
An apology?
When we went out that day,
you made such a big mistake.
Why don't I get a drink?
Senior, I'll treat you next time.
Senior, you raise shrimp?
So pretty.
Wait a moment.
Here.
Please sign for this.
Gao Zhiyao,
you know No. 9568's wife very well?
I don't know her.
Don't know her?
If you don't know her,
why did she greet you?
And even thank you?
How would I know?
Thank you, hottie.
Senior, please don't be like this.
It's weird.
If there's nothing else, I'll go now.
Wait.
Look.
Why does the handwriting look so similar?
[Chihuahua Zhang Longji,
Cell Block 2, Cell 25]
Do they?
I just wrote it sloppily.
-I’ll write it again.
-No need.
Correctional officers
getting too close to inmates,
seeking improper benefits,
and damaging institutional discipline...
These actions are punishable by law.
Sneaking into the prison at night,
helping inmates smuggle contraband,
arranging unauthorized meetings
with family members...
If you do these things
and I find evidence,
you'll end up in prison yourself.
This is Shun!
A student has lost control
in the classroom!
The social worker and I are in danger!
Hurry up, I'm gonna die!
Quick!
Calm down!
Stop smashing things!
That's enough.
Zhang Zixu, stop smashing things.
Zhang Zixu!